https://uncleciggie.com/index.php?main_page=privacy

* 1" CHILD'S COLLECTION
All Products ...
Links
Home ::
Privacy Notice
Privacy Notice
Information Collection and Use
Information collected on this site will not be sold, shared or rented to others.
Order
We request information from customers on our order form. Here customers must provide contact information (like name and shipping address) and financial information (like credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, this contact information is used to get in touch with a customer.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the customer’s hard drive containing information about the user. For instance, by setting a cookie on our site, users will not have to provide address details each time they order and the shopping basket can remember products purchased at an earlier time. Cookies are stored on the customer’s computer only. We have no access to their content.
Log Files
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
Links
This website may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our website and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Security
The security of your information is very important to us. We use the 2048-bit Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect the security of your online order information. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than Uncle Ciggie's. Once you enter the checkout page your computer will begin communicating with our server in secure mode. You can tell that you are in secure mode by the following:
The "http" in the web address will be replaced by "https"
Depending on the browser, you may see a padlock in the lower section for the browser window, also indicating that you are in a secure mode.
Only browsers that use the 128-bit Secure Socket Layer technology are able to order through the Uncle Ciggie site. If your browser does not support SSL, or you get an error message, you can get an upgrade at Microsoft's or Firefox's home page for further information. If you have any questions about the security of our website, please send us an email.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our main page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.
Home
Copyright © 2020 Uncle Ciggie's Miniatures. Design by Anne Gerdes Web Design
